# Nameer Iqbal Ansari

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan



niansari@students.uit.edu



03363033155



linkedin.com/in/nameer-ansari-136944209

# Summary

This is NAMEER IQBAL ANSARI aka N.i.AnXari. Initially, Studied matriculation from S.M.PUBLIC ACADEMY. Then, He went to ADAMJEE GOV SCIENCE COLLEGE for intermediate. Currently, Studying BE (Computer system engineering) at USMAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY. Meanwhile,

\*Working in MERL(Micro Electronic research lab) as RESEARCH INTERN at UITU Karachi.

## **Experience**



### Contributor

Google Summer of Code

Jun 2022 - Present (3 months +)

"Add FuseSoC support at SoC level for Azadi-SoC and Rebase ibex core with latest commit" is the project I'm working on.

#### MERL Research Intern

Micro Electronics Research Lab

Mar 2021 - Present (1 year 6 months +)

## **Education**



## Usman Institute of Technology

electrical engineering, Computer Technology/Computer Systems Technology 2019 - 2023



**Adamjee Government Science College** 



S.M.Public Academy

## Skills

Amazon EC2 • Fusesoc • Cloud FPGA • Verilog • RTL Design • Adobe Photoshop • Adobe Illustrator • C++ • Logisim • Processors

<sup>\*</sup>GSoC'22 contributor.

<sup>\*</sup>Doing an Open Source project NOVA with UCI (University of California Irvine).